(cheerful guitar music)
♪ Right, right, turn off the lights ♪
♪ We gonna lose our minds tonight ♪
♪ What's the dealio? ♪
♪ I love when it's all too much ♪
♪ 5 a.m. turn the radio up ♪
♪ Where's the rock and roll? ♪
♪ Party crasher ♪
♪ Panty snatcher ♪
♪ Call me up if you a gangsta ♪
♪ Don't be fancy, just get dancy ♪
♪ Why so serious? ♪
♪ So raise your glass if you are wrong ♪
♪ In all the right ways ♪
♪ All my underdogs ♪
♪ We will never be never
be anything but loud ♪
♪ And nitty, gritty, dirty little freaks ♪
♪ Won't you come on and come
on and raise your glass ♪
♪ Just come on and come
♪ Slam slam, oh hot damn ♪
♪ What part of party
don't you understand ♪
♪ Wish you'd just freak out ♪
♪ Can't stop, comin' in hot ♪
♪ I should be locked
up right on the spot ♪
♪ It's so on right now ♪
♪ So fuckin' on right now ♪
♪ Party crasher ♪
♪ Panty snatcher ♪
♪ Call me up if you a gangsta ♪
♪ Don't be fancy, just get dancy ♪
♪ Why so serious? ♪
♪ So raise your glass if you are wrong ♪
♪ In all the right ways ♪
♪ All my underdogs ♪
♪ We will never be never
be anything but loud ♪
♪ And nitty, gritty, dirty little freaks ♪
♪ Won't you come on and come
on and raise your glass ♪
♪ Just come on and come
♪ Won't you come on and come
on and raise your glass ♪
♪ Just come on and come
♪ Oh shit my glass is empty, that sucks ♪
♪ So if you're too school for cool ♪
♪ And you're treated like a fool ♪
♪ Treated like a fool ♪
♪ You can choose to let it go ♪
♪ We can always, we can always ♪
♪ Party on our own ♪
♪ So raise your, oh fuck ♪
♪ So raise your glass if you are wrong ♪
♪ In all the right ways ♪
♪ All my underdogs ♪
♪ We will never be never
be anything but loud ♪
♪ And nitty, gritty, dirty little freaks ♪
♪ So raise your glass if you are wrong ♪
♪ In all the right ways ♪
♪ All my underdogs ♪
♪ We will never be never
be, anything but loud ♪
♪ And nitty, gritty, dirty little freaks ♪
♪ Won't you come on and come
on and raise your glass ♪
♪ Just come on and come
♪ Won't you come on and come
on and raise your glass ♪
♪ Just come on and come
♪ For me ♪